

Resume Of SAJIB AHMED

CONTACT INFO

Gazi Para, Uttarkhan, Dhaka

sajibahmed2399@gmail.com

01771134540, 01616172852

PERSONALTY

- Loyalty
- Creativity
- Team Work
- Self-Motivated
- Communicative
- Leadership Skill
- Courteous Manners

SUMMARY

A well-presented industrious and highly personable individual who has extensive in-depth experience in different industries. Have more than two years of experience as a Customer Service Associate. Creative problem solver who built a new customer retention program that increased customer loyalty. Possessing a huge range of abilities from providing support and leadership to junior staff right through to being able to gain the trust of customers by interacting with people from all backgrounds. I enjoy my work so I do it passionately.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To secure a challenging position in a reputable organization to expand my learning, knowledge, and skills. Increasing my skills through learning and hard work. Secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my training and skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

EXPERIENCE

Orgagenic

Department : Sales & Support

Designation : Sales & Support Executive

Duration : 7th February 2023 - 31st May 2023.

Responsibilities:

- · Handing the customer base of Orgagenic through online chat and over the phone. Answering the different kinds of queries from customers.
- Suggesting products according to their needs.
- · Resolving the problems that may occur during the ordering of products.
- Ensuring sales by eliminating customer confusion.
- Troubleshooting the transportation problem.

Windows Microsoft Word Microsoft PowerPoint Internet Browsing SEO Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGES

English

Bangla

EXPERIENCE

ShopUp

Department : Customer Experience (Inbound & Outbound)

Designation : Customer Service Executive

Duration: 8th June 2021 - 31st August 2022.

Responsibilities:

Taking NPS is score from merchants and customers.

Taking feedback from merchants and customers to improve service

Solving the problems of merchants and customers.

Genex Infosys Limited

Department : Inbound

Designation : Customer Service Executive

Duration : 3rd November, 2019 to 2nd August 2020.

Responsibilities:

Handling the base subscribers of Grameenphone over the phone and providing all kinds of Grameenphone-related services.

Highlight the customer's technical problems to the proper channel to resolve them etc.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

IELTS : Overall Band 6.5

(Listening 6.5, Reading 6.0, Writing 6.5 & Speaking 6.0)

B.B.A : Uttara Anwara Model University College.

Session : 2022-2023

Subject : Marketing, 3rd year running.

H.S.C: Uttara Anwara Model University College.

Passing year : 2019 G.P. A : 3.25

Department : Business Studies.

S.S.C: Uttar Khan Collegiate School, Dhaka.

Passing year : 2017 G.P. A : 4.09

Department : Business Studies.

HOBBIES



Music







